Eye of the Beholder

Robert Silverberg

Original Science Fiction Stories – September 1959

Art dealers, art phonies, and struggling artists alike were agog when the being from Paradilla revealed his mission. He was here to select some of Earth's masterpieces for the art-collection of His Altitude, the Emperor of Paradilla—at fabulous prices!

THE ALIEN landed at New York Spaceport on the fifth of August, 2281, a blisteringly hot day despite the best efforts of the Weather Control Bureau. The alien, of course, did not care about the weather, encased as he was in a mobile biotic unit. He simply rolled down the spaceship's ramp into the cluster of eager reporters who had been waiting ever since learning that a visitor from distant Paradilla was en route to Earth.

To the sweating newsmen, the Paradillan looked like a gleaming black metallic pear five feet high, with a ring of perceptor lenses circling the upper part of its body; three multiply-jointed arms projecting beneath those; and a speaker grid set square in the widest part of the pear. Ball-bearing gliders provided mobility. Within the sealed unit lived the Paradillan, eighty pounds of beady-eyed green lemuroid, breathing its corrosive atmosphere of hydrogen sulfide and shimmering pleasantly at a temperature of 680 degrees Kelvin.

"Why have you come to Earth?" demanded an eager wire-service man.

The voder output of the alien's biotic unit replied blandly, "To gratify the wish of His Altitude Naribullah Zorz, Elevated Mightiness of Imperial Paradilla. His Altitude desires to form a collection of Terran paintings. He has established a credit of several million dollars with reputable Terran banking firms, to facilitate purchase of the desired works of art."

"Give us some idea of what you're looking for!"

"I seek the pinnacle of Terran artistic achievement," said the Paradillan. "I will stint no expense in my search."

-

PORTABLE stenotypes clatteringly recorded the alien's words. Minutes later, in the press room of the spaceport, a dozen reporters hastily pounded out their stories. After all, a visit from a Paradillan was news. Paradilla was six hundred thousand light-years from Earth: nine weeks even by warpdrive travel. Only a handful of intrepid Earth-men had ever visited the planet; no more than a dozen Paradillans had bothered to journey to Earth in the century since Terra had become an interstellar power.

But it was known that Paradilla was the center of commerce in its particular galaxy—a fabulously rich world where even the paupers were wealthy. Jokes about Paradillan trillionaires and their odd tastes were standard network fare. If a Paradillan had come to Earth to buy paintings for His Altitude, it meant that a good bit of cash was going to be thrown about.

The news broke in the late afternoon editions of the telefax sheets. Most papers treated it lightly: PICASSO FOR PARADILLA, headlined the Globe, while the Transworld snickered, ARTY ALIEN ARRIVES, HERE TO PICK PIX FOR PARADILLA.

-

IN THE AIR-conditioned offices of Vandeventer Sateen, whose plush gallery was a fashionable highlight of New York's famed Eleventh Avenue, the arrival of the alien aroused considerable interest. Mr. Sateen himself, an elegant little man of impeccable taste, rarely troubled to read the 'fax-sheets. But one of his assistants made a point of keeping abreast of the news, and it was he who disturbed the art dealer's negotiations via tridim with an elderly and indigent Yorkshire noblewoman by saying, "Could you look at this, sir?"

Without losing a syllable of his transatlantic conversation, Mr. Sateen skimmed the telefax clipping. Nodding, he deftly brought the negotiations to a close with an offer that met immediate acceptance. As Lady Bracknell faded from the screen, Mr. Sateen said crisply, "Very good. Arrange an appointment with this Paradillan at once. No, I'll call him myself!"

-

Far across the city, in the dilapidated and picturesque Park Avenue district, an equally dapper but far less respectable person was digesting the Globe article with care. He was Pierre d'Entendre, formerly of Marseilles and points north, a connoisseur of forgeries, imitations, stolen goods, and other illegitimacies of the world of art. d'Entendre stroked his beard thoughtfully, eyeing the bogus Brueghel and the spurious Seurat that currently decorated his peeling walls. Perhaps some business' could be done with this well-heeled extraterrestrial, he thought. Smiling, he reached for the visiphone.

-

While at the same time, across the river in Brooklyn, a young painter of the hyperrealist school was feeling an unfamiliar tingle of hope. For once he could stop fretting about the squalling of his two small, hungry children and could ignore the accusing glares of his unhappy' wife. Lester Martin laughed out loud.

"What's so funny?" Beth Martin asked sourly.

"Good news, for once. There's a Paradillan here looking to buy Terran paintings. And you know how much dough those guys are supposed to have!"

Beth sighed, scowling at the un framed canvasses stacked near their infant son's playpen. "So?"

"So?" Martin repeated. "So I'm going to see that Paradillan, that's what! So I'm going to sell him my paintings!"

"You—sell him your paintings?" Beth laughed icily. "You've been painting nine years without a sale, Rembrandt. And now—now ..."

"Don't you have any faith in me?"

"Do you want me to answer that?"

Lester Martin shrugged. "You wait and see, Beth. Just you wait and see."

-

THE PARADILLAN was quartered at an expensive hotel in metropolitan Nyack, as per arrangements made in advance by the Bureau of Extraterrestrial Welfare, which took care of such matters for arriving aliens. Since he and his mobile biotic unit together weighed close to five hundred pounds, he received a special topfloor suite with reinforced flooring, reserved for such cases.

The suite was luxurious: five large rooms, each with individual sealing bulkheads should the alien guest care to introduce his own atmosphere. But the Paradillan had no such intention. He was perfectly comfortable in the womb-like security of his biotic unit, and did not plan to have the hermetic seal broken until he had returned to his home world. Within the mobile unit he had facilities for exercise, a food synthesizer, entertainment tapes, and a flawless atmospheric circulating system. It was like carrying a bit of Paradilla with him.

-

NO MORE than half an hour after the first telefax accounts of the Paradillan's arrival hit the streets, the visiphone calls began to come in.

The Paradillan had some slight difficulty operating the phone with his arm-extensors, but he got the knack of it fast enough. The screen brightened and his perceptor pickups showed him an Earthman's face. The Earthman had little hair on his head, and wore red velvet garments that bothered the Paradillan's sense of texture.

"Yes?" the alien inquired.

"Ah—good afternoon, sir." The Earthman's voice was soft and well-modulated. "I am Vandeventer Sateen, director of Sateen Galleries."

"Yes," said the alien in a neutral tone.

"Of course, I don't imagine that the reputation of our house will be familiar to one who had journeyed such an unimaginable distance, but ..."

"I've heard of you," the Paradillan said shortly.

"Ah—certainly! I should have known that one to whom so important a mission has been entrusted would be familiar with every detail of his task. I understand you wish to take to your home world examples of Terra's finest artistic achievements, sir. May I humbly remark that the services of the Sateen Galleries are at your disposal during the length of your stay on our planet?"

"Good of you," commented the alien.

-

MR. SATEEN continued smoothly, "Your acceptance of our guidance honors us beyond measure, good sir. Would it be considered pre-sumptuous if I were to add that at present we are capable of supplying you with a most rarefied selection of Old Masters: Matisse, van Gogh, El Greco, Pollock, Renoir, Ingres, virtually every style, every period."

"How comprehensive," rumbled the expressionless voder voice of the Paradillan.

"May we prepare our gallery for a private inspection by yourself?" Mr. Sateen asked. "We will place ourselves at your complete disposal at a moment's notice."

The Paradillan was silent a brief while. He said finally, "What about tomorrow?"

Mr. Sateen looked momentarily disconcerted, but recovered quickly. "Tomorrow? Of course, if you so wish ..."

"At 0500 hours."

The art dealer elegantly moistened his lips and genteelly dabbed the perspiration from his forehead. The House of Sateen opened at 0900, never earlier. Mr. Sateen fought a brief inward battle. With only slight hesitation he said, "Very well. My staff and I will await your arrival. At 0500 hours."

-

HARDLY had the Paradillan broken the visiphone contact when the chime sounded again. The alien switched on the screen and peered at a darkly intense face which bore a pointed tuft of black hair on its

"I am so pleased to have made the contact with the so estimable guest from distant stars, M'sieu. Permit the introduction: Pierre d'Entendre, craving your attention."

The bearded Earthman spoke Terran with a strange nasal intonation that gave the Paradillan's translator-intake some trouble. "Please speak more clearly," the alien said flatly.

"A hundred thousand pardons, M'sieu! I am what they call the person displaced; my home lies across the sea and my tongue is poorly accustomed to this hard language. But I meander. Allow the directness: I deal in rarities of art. You are here to purchase. Perhaps we may do the business conjointly, and profit mutually thereby, n'est-ce pas?"

"I already have an appointment for tomorrow at the Sateen Galleries."

"Ah, yes, certainly, the estimable Sateen! So dignified, so fashionable, so—how shall we say?—expensive! See Sateen, by all means. But reserve the judgment, do not buy. Stay your hand until you have considered all resources. I perhaps can offer you more, aid you to serve your client more agreeably. For when is your visit with Sateen?"

"0500 hours."

"0500—you make the joke! Surely Sateen will not do business at ..."

"0500 hours."

d'Entendre gulped audibly. "Indeed, M'sieu—M'sieu—I have not the name ..."

"Paradillans of my class do not bear names."

"Ah, so! Even then, M'sieu: may I extend to you my invitation to visit my humble establishment when you have left the Maison Sateen? Perhaps at 0900, and I shall display my treasures ..."

"Very well."

"You have given me deepest pleasure, M'sieu. But—do me one small courtesy—come alone, and in silence? I imply, invite not the gentlemen or the press. We shall deal better in privacy, yes?"

-

AGAIN THE screen blanked, after some moments of d'Entendre's effusive goodbyes. But it did not remain blank long. The calls flooded in. Curators of fifty museums longed to offer advice without charge to the alien. Every art dealer in the world seemed anxious to sell paintings to the Paradillan. Some artists tried to arrange personal showings for him.

After midnight the calls diminished to a trickle, but it was not until 0300 hours that the phone remained silent for good. The Paradillan, having no need of sleep and tremendously enjoying the notoriety, remained by the phone even then, hoping for another call, but none came.

-

AT 0500 HOURS the gates of the House of Sateen opened and the Paradillan's quarter-ton biotic unit rolled ponderously in, leaving behind a scored spoor of tiny indentations in the deep-pile red carpet. Mr. Sateen, bleary-eyed at the unusual hour, deftly concealed his inward distress over the damage. The prestige of supplying art to His Altitude, the Elevated Mightiness of Imperial Paradilla, would more than make up for any slight losses. Besides, the insurance covered it.

"If you would come this way, kind sir," Mr. Sateen murmured, bowing and dancing genteelly round the metal bulk of the biotic unit. "Everything is prepared."

Within, the suave salesmen of the House of Sateen, all of them drawing extra pay for this early-morning duty, awaited the alien. Safely concealed upstairs lurked reporters from the major press services, waiting for word from Mr. Sateen; he had promised them news as soon as a deal was clinched.

The galleries were decked out with their finest. Mr. Sateen had seen to it that none but the best was on display. A sumptuous El Greco greeted the Paradillan in the Grand Gallery, flanked by a darkly melodramatic Rembrandt and a small but exquisite Raphael madonna. Mr. Sateen launched into a dainty disquisition on the El Greco, tracing its history and leading gently toward the $300,000 price-tag, when the Paradillan made a sudden comment about a Velasquez hung on the far wall. Mr. Sateen realized uncomfortably that the biotic unit had 360-degree vision.

Shifting gears rapidly, Mr. Sateen said, "Indeed, yes. A fine piece, formerly from the collection of Dr. and Mrs. Hiram Blumberg, who purchased it in 2253 from ..."

"The frame is quite attractive," commented the Paradillan, its voder voice accenting frame ever so lightly.

-

MR. SATEEN took the hint.

Neither the Velasquez nor the Rembrandt nor the Raphael nor even the El Greco pleased the alien's austere tastes. Mr. Sateen guided the Paradillan through a corridor into the Green Room. Here a Mondrian in stark white and red held the position of honor. Other notables of the 20th and 21st century were represented as well: a sparkling Picasso, a playful Chagall, a moody Leeuwenhoek, an intricate Kandinsky, a delicate Klee.

The Paradillan's response was coolish. Undaunted, Mr. Sateen glided onward into the Red Room, with its glittering array of Byzantine painting and its impressive Duccio altarpiece. The impassive Paradillan merely remarked, "The color of the room distresses me."

Mr. Sateen manfully maintained his composure. He led the alien to the Octagonal Room, resplendent with Reynolds, Gainsborough, Turner, Copley; to the Prismatic Room, which displayed van Gogh, Renoir, Monet, Pissaro, Utrillo; to the Blue Room and Goya, Rubens, Tiepolo, van Eyck; to the Rococo Room and Fragonard, Watteau, Vernet, Moreau.

And then the Paradillan had seen it all; no more remained. Still he had indicated no preference. Mr. Sateen, far too refined to press for a decision, danced attendance on the alien as he ushered him to the grand gate.

"It was an honor to have showed our collection to you," said the art dealer unctuously.

-

THE PARADILLAN replied, "The experience was valuable."

"May I venture to express the hope that we will hear from you shortly?"

"You will not hear from me," was the calmly blunt response. "In my opinion none of the works shown me today is of quality suitable to merit purchase for His Altitude's collection."

Mr. Sateen went glassy-eyed with shock. A flashbulb exploded and three reporters, waving stenotype microphones, popped from alcoves concealed by drapery.

"Would you repeat that statement for the press, please?"

"No! No!" Mr. Sateen cried. "This is an intolerable intrusion!"

The Paradillan said mildly, "In my opinion, none of the works shown me today is of quality suitable to merit purchase for His Altitude's collection."

Stenotypers clacked. More flashbulbs popped. Mr. Sateen's suave aides, no longer suave, hastily expelled the Fourth Estate. The Paradillan, ignored in the confusion, activated his biotic unit and rolled out of the Maison Sateen.

-

THE 0900 editions of most of the telefax sheets gave it a big play: OLD MASTERS BORE ARTY ALIEN, said Transworld; PARADILLAN SNEERS AT REMBRANDT, VAN GOGH, trumpeted the Globe. Pierre d'Entendre smiled obliquely at the headlines spread out on his imitation Louis Quatorze table and bowed to his unusual guest.

"They have made the mistake," d'Entendre chuckled. "It is not the artists you scoff; it is the foolishly inflated prices of M. Sateen. Now, this treasurable Manet, mon ami, be good enough to regard it. M. Sateen would ask a hundred thousand. But I, I have no plush establishment to maintain"—he gestured grandiosely at the seedy apartment—"and I have the, how you say, inside contacts. His Altitude may have this gem for a trifle. Twenty-five thousand!"

The Paradillan's perceptors focussed on the painting. After a moment the alien said, "This Manet—he painted in the 19th Century of Terran reckoning?"

"But of course!"

"Plainly this painting can be no more than ten years old."

d'Entendre reddened. "An impossibility! It dates from 1873, easily! Four hundred years, mon ami, not a mere ten!"

-

THE PARADILLAN said, "I am examining the texture of the paint and the weaving, of the canvas. My perceptors are infallible. The painting is less than ten years old."

"But—but—oh, ten thousand pardons!" d'Entendre exclaimed, whisking the Manet out of sight. "An error, M'sieu! The work is a copy, done by a young friend of mine, a most promising beginner. In forgetful error did I offer it to you! But let us examine the fineness of this Picasso, in the cubist manner, an undoubted 20th Century masterwork, the property of His Altitude for a paltry forty thousand!"

"The painting is 20th Century," the Paradillan agreed after a brief inspection. d'Entendre sighed in relief. "But," went on the alien, "It is unsigned. And it bears no recognizable Picasso traits. You err again, M. d'Entendre."

"Indeed, a mistake, a mistake—I beg forgiveness," the eager entrepreneur stammered. "See, I inadvertently mislabelled it! The painting is by another. Ah—one Schwartz, I believe. Circa 1971. A valuable piece nonetheless, and for sale at a meager two thousand ..."

-

"SECOND-RATERS do not interest me," declared the Paradillan coldly, and Schwartz hastily disappeared behind the meretricious Manet. d'Entendre produced another choice specimen, a carefully forged Vermeer. The alien dismissed it contemptuously. Imitation Titian and ersatz Caravaggio met with equal scorn. At length, despairing, d'Entendre was at the point of bringing out his few genuine but worthless paintings when the Paradillan called the farce to a halt.

"Your paintings," the alien said, "are misrepresented, mislabelled, and miscreated. You have attempted fraud, sir. Can you deny this?"

"All right, so I can't! So the stuff is phony!" d'Entendre shouted, accent and inflection melting under the stress. "What of it? Can the Elevated Mightiness tell the difference between cubist Picasso and cubist Schwartz? Look here, friend—you don't act like a dope. You know the score. I'll let you have all twenty of these paintings for two hundred thousand—ten grand apiece. You can tell the High Muckymuck that they're all genuine and you paid fifty grand apiece. You pocket eight hundred thousand cookies on the deal, and I'll get some dough too! How about it, huh?"

There was a glacial silence. The Paradillan said in booming tones, "Your proposal is beneath contempt. I must inform you that defrauding the Elevated Mightiness is a crime punishable with loss of soul. I could not consider any such proposition. Good day, M. d'Entendre."

-

WITHOUT mentioning names, the Paradillan gave full details of his interview with d'Entendre to the press. His stock rose at once: an alien who could sneer at the House of Sateen might be merely arrogant, but one who could unmask a fraud deserved respect. He was shrewd, and Earthmen respected shrewdness.

The next three days were busy ones for the Paradillan. Without benefit of secretarial assistance he made and kept some forty appointments, visiting galleries and showrooms throughout the Western Hemisphere. He attracted tremendous attention wherever he went, partly because of the tanklike massiveness of the biotic unit, partly because of his frank and unconcealed scorn for the classic masterworks of Terran art.

He journeyed to Europe at the end of the week, followed by a growing retinue of newsmen. The Paradillan was becoming bigger news each day. His patronizing words for the Mona Lisa stunned Paris; his casually devastating dismissal of the Sistine Chapel infuriated Italy. He made no purchases in Europe. After five days he returned to his Nyack hotel. He called a press conference for midnight; and, so fascinated had the public become with the haughty Paradillan, his suite was crowded with reporters as early as half past ten.

-

AT MIDNIGHT, the alien faced the grinding video cameras and said, "I have searched in vain for many days for a work of art suitable for the collection of the Elevated Mightiness of Imperial Paradilla. I have been approached by frauds and I have been shown the finest collections of Terran art that are to be seen. And I have bought nothing.

"Why? Because what I have seen is sterile, lifeless, without meaning or universal validity. I am greatly distressed by the feebleness of what I have seen. Can Terran art lack all vitality, while Terrans themselves are among the most vigorous of the universe's peoples? It seems unlikely.

"Yet so the evidence of your art insists. But I have not abandoned hope. I have sworn not to return empty-handed to His Altitude. Ladies and gentlemen, I will not stop searching until my quest is satisfied! Thank you and good night."

The statement caused a global rumpus. Angry art-lovers demanded the immediate expulsion of the scornful extraterrestrial; delighted philistines crowed that they had known the truth about art all along. The Paradillan made front pages everywhere. Throngs of the curious followed the gleaming biotic unit as it rolled from gallery to gallery.

Three weeks after his arrival on Earth, the Paradillan called another press conference. This time, though, it was not to be held at his hotel.

The address he gave was in Brooklyn—at the home of a hitherto unknown artist named Lester Martin.

-

WHEN THE reporters assembled duly at the Martin home, they found the Paradillan already there. Also present were Lester Martin—a stubby-faced young man of thirty, with the classically untidy hair and the mandatory black, turtle-neck sweater of the struggling artist; Beth Martin—a weary, sad-faced girl of twenty-eight, with frizzly reddish hair and a sallow complexion; and their two children—Marcia, age four, and Vincent, age sixteen months, both unruly, underfed, and undisciplined.

The three-room apartment was shabby and dingy. Without air conditioning, the humidity was dreadful. Paintings in various states of completion were stacked everywhere: in the kitchen, in the bathtub, under the bed, behind the bookcases. A few hung framed on the walls.

Lester Martin looked tense, apprehensive, inwardly proud. His wife looked hopelessly confused. The yowling children simply looked defiant.

It was the Paradillan who did all the talking. Gesturing to the reporters for silence, he said, "Many of you are aware of my considerable search for works of art I could purchase for the collection of His Altitude, Naribullah Zorz, Elevated Mightiness of Imperial Paradilla. At great expense I have examined the wares of Earth's merchants of art, weighed their offerings in the balance, found them wanting.

"But at last my quest has ended. Yesterday a young artist came to me, shyly humble, to show me a few of his works. I looked at them and asked to see more. He invited me to his home. I have examined his paintings with care. And, I happily announce, I find them worthy of the collection of His Altitude!"

The alien handed a slip of paper to Lester Martin and went on, "I have just paid over a check for $1,443,281.07, as the agreed purchase-price for thirty-nine of Mr. Lester Martin's paintings."

-

MRS. LESTER MARTIN let out a subdued shriek and toppled into a heap. Martin, beaming, ignored her. The reporters muttered.

The Paradillan said, "Mr. Martin has prepared a display of the purchased pictures in the adjoining room. You may enter one by one to examine them. I caution you in advance that some are highly experimental and may appear strange, even barbaric, to you. But bear in mind that beauty is in the eye of the beholder; and to me, these masterful paintings sum up all of Earth's power and grandeur. His Altitude will give these the place of honor in his collection."

The alien allowed the buzzing reporters into the bedroom to view the thirty-nine pictures. Isolated comments drifted out. "Passed up Rembrandt for tripe like this!" "Look at those crazy zigzags!" "You understand that stuff? I sure don't!" "Me neither!"

At last the newsmen and photographers had finished viewing the exhibit, and all had left, bustling back to file their sensational stories. Only the Paradillan and the Martins remained. The alien handed a sealed envelope to the grinning Martin. "My bill," the Paradillan said.

Martin slit the envelope and read the bill:

FOR SERVICES RENDERED

Passage, Paradilla-Earth, round trip

$19,565.50 Terran

Hotel and travel expenses

4,200.21 Terran

Miscellaneous expenses

1,806.39 Terran

Fee for services

10,000.00 Terran

TOTAL

$35,572.10 Terran

MARTIN smiled. "Naturally, I can't pay it for a while. But I'll have the money for you as soon as it starts coming in."

"Let us hope so."

"I don't see how it can miss. Thanks for everything."

"The pleasure was mine. Farewell."

The biotic unit reversed its treads and solemnly rolled through the open door.

-

Lester Martin cackled gleefully. He waved the bill aloft. "It worked! It worked! Beth, we're rich!"

"A million and a half bucks for your paintings," Beth murmured dazedly. "I still can't believe it really happened Lester."

"It didn't," Lester said. "You can put the check in your scrapbook, if you like."

"What?"

"The check isn't any good. The whole thing was a fake, Beth! Got it? A downright fake!"

Her eyes slowly widened. "Lester, what are you talking about?"

"The Elevated Mightiness of Paradilla doesn't have any art collection. A Terran painting wouldn't last two years in Paradilla's atmosphere."

"But—what ..."

"Remember when Marty Bryan went on that expedition to Paradilla last year? We cooked the whole thing up just before he left. He would hire a Paradillan to come here and stage the whole thing, go shopping for the Mightiness' collection, stir up a lot of publicity—and then pick my stuff!"

-

BETH'S MOUTH opened and closed fishwise. "All a fake?"

"I'll be on every front page tonight. And you know how art collectors are. They don't give a damn for ability; they just want names. Well, tomorrow morning I'll be the biggest name on Earth! Come on. Let's get those paintings out of the bedroom and down to the furnace."

"To the furnace?" Beth repeated dimly.

"Sure! Suppose someone finds them and realizes they were never shipped to Paradilla? It's safer to destroy them. But there are plenty more where those came from."

"But—but—suppose somebody goes to Paradilla and asks to see the Mightiness' art collection? What then?"

"Firstly, hardly anybody ever goes Paradilla. Second, what if they do find out, years from now? By then we'll be rich!"

Another objection occurred to Beth. "Say—I thought all Paradillans were millionaires! How come one of them would be willing to travel all that distance just for a few thousand dollars?"

"Who says a millionaire isn't always interested in getting a little more? Besides, Marty played up the fun angle of the trip. Be a celebrity on Earth; hoax the Terrans. He probably had to beat away applicants for the job."

-

THE PHONE was ringing raucously by the time the Martins returned empty-handed from the furnace room. Mr. Sateen was calling, swallowing his pride and humbly asking for permission to represent Lester as a client. d'Entendre and a few dozen other enterprising art dealers had the same notion later in the day, and got the same answer: Lester intended to represent himself in the art markets.

Within a week, Lester had sold off his entire backlog of paintings and had commissions for fifty new ones at exorbitant prices. The Paradillan publicity had done its work.

A week later, Lester quietly forwarded a check for $40,000 Terran to his Paradillan cohort—and painted happily ever after.

The End